Good morning.
Yuka Murayama of Mealy Call Joy and
With Maimi Ozawa
Mizuki Oshida and
Esbel Non.
Yay!
Hi there.
Today we are here in Okazaki city, Aichi prefecture.
Mr. Tetsuya from Soukai Ouen, who has been supporting us
Tetsuya from Soukai Cheer, who has been supporting us
Tetsuya from Soukai-support, who has been supporting us, has planned a trip to Okazaki for us.
Thank you very much!
We are very happy!
Yes, so...
Today we are going to enjoy Okazaki city to the fullest.
It's a one-day trip!
Yay!
I'm so happy!
It's amazing!
It's too big!
But I'm so happy. I've always wanted to go.
I'm so happy that we're all here.
I'm so happy.
First of all, let's start with the first one.
We're going to rent a car in Tetsuya's color from Narimo Rent-a-Car.
Tetsuya's color car for rent.
I'm so glad!
I saw that.
I'm so glad.
That's great!
I've received some comments.
NARIMO Rent-a-Car has an orange Avery in Tetsuya's color.
Tetsuya's color orange Avery!
Please enjoy your trip to Okazaki in the orange Avery.
and enjoy your trip to Okazaki!
I'm so happy!
Comment?
Really a comment?
It seems so.
That's great!
Yes, it is.
Thank you so much!
That's great!
I'm so happy!
I'm too excited.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
We can't drive!
Yes, we can.
Actually...
It looks bad.
Yes.
You don't have a driver's license.
I'm going to have a driver
I was thinking of having the driver drive me.
I'm thinking of splitting up and taking a ride in the curved seats.
Okay.
Can I just leave a comment?
Yes, sir.
Good par, then?
Good par.
I'll get him to talk.
I'll let you talk.
Yes, sir.
Good par.
That's it.
Yes, sir.
You're not going to let him talk to anyone by himself?
The one with the melons, right?
Hold on.
Let's spread the word about Osaka.
Good luck.
I don't work alone.
Goodpers!
Good-perfect.
GoodPer
Good-per
You're not getting it.
It's not happening.
It's gone.
Okay, that's a yes.
Good par?
Good par with me.
I'll give up.
Goo.
We're in love.
Okay, we're breaking up.
Okay, let's go.
I heard they're almost there.
Yes, sir.
You can see it.
With a whiz.
Yes.
Bloop.
Let's do a little pop.
Just a little bit.
Let's do it.
pop, pop, pop, pop, pop
modo
So, here it is.
This is a gentleman's handmade.
Oh, wow!
Awesome orange.
That's a great orange.
Wipers are out, too.
Mr. Scan, follow up on that.
Oh, my God.
You're famous.
What? It's kind of cute.
It's so cute!
So cute!
This guy.
This is amazing.
Oh, my God.
I'm so happy.
I'm so nervous.
Oh, my God.
Today's the day.
This one's from here.
We're going to be riding with a team.
We can go to different spots, right?
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
So, which one of you
Which team rides first?
The first half and the second half.
Twenty-two, right?
All right.
Let's go.
I don't care if we lose.
It's okay.
It's better to win.
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors!
This is cute!
Yes!
Reno and Ai will ride first.
Okay!
Where are you going?
Eyes?
It's lunchtime and I'm hungry.
Very hungry.
I think I'm going to be hungry, too.
So...
I'd like to go to the famous chicken restaurant.
I'd like to go to Cullenboro Chicken.
I'd love to eat there.
I've seen a lot of videos.
I'm hungry.
I'm gonna make my stomach into a chicken now.
I'll be chicken.
I'll be a chicken.
Get on the chicken
Ride the chicken
We have a commemorative award now!
You'll get a special prize.
If you show it to me at the end at a place like this
If you get a sticker, you'll get a great deal.
We would like to chat with you about this tour too!
Yes, that's why I'd like to have a chat with you more than us.
From Tetsuya-san
We're on the Emry. Let's go!
It's amazing! There's nothing in the back!
We're driving. People from all over the world are here.
We're on our way to Avalenborg Chicken now.
I'm really looking forward to it. I'm really hungry.
I'm really hungry, so it'll be nice to go to that hill we saw in the video.
Pilgrimage.
What's this?
Pilgrimage cards. Cards?
What card? A pilgrimage card?
If you hold this up, it seems there's a special offer.
I'd like to hold it up.
That's so manly. I'm so happy.
I'm glad. The illustrations are all so cute.
It's great, isn't it? It's like opening a door, or a corner, or something.
It's like opening a door in a corner.
But I heard it's coming soon. It's so close.
I'm so hungry, I have a craving.
It's definitely good right now
So I'm going to risk my life for Okazaki.
I'm hungry, and I'm ready to enjoy it to the fullest.
In my stomach.
Okay, we'll be in the blue car in the back here.
I'd like to welcome you.
Cute.
And the logo.
It's cute.
It's a very cute car.
Okay, I'm off.
Let's go to Max Car!
Here we go!
We're heading to Abatiki!
I played with the stickers I got.
So cute!
It means so colorful!
There's a whole car full of them.
Isn't it all cute?
Everything's cute.
It's so cute.
The one in front is orange, too.
Wait, they're matching.
Matching?
Maybe you should join us.
You mean?
We're orange too.
Orange Alliance.
I can't stop thinking about orange.
We do.
Like, "Hey, can I borrow this?
While we were filming...
There were a lot of fans
who are making a pilgrimage to the holy land.
They shook hands with the owner of the store.
and shook hands with the shop owners.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Isn't it fun to go on a pilgrimage?
We've been on a pilgrimage all day.
I'm so happy!
Thank you for your hard work.
Wow, wow, wow. We're going on a trip together. I can totally see it.
Oh, wow, it's on screen. I can see it everywhere we go.
I can see it. Wow!
I know! I know!
We're here. We're here.
Oh, wow!
So, we've arrived at the Chicken on a Streak!
Yay! I'm so happy! It's real!
It's real! Doesn't it smell great?
I'm so hungry! I'm so hungry!
I'm so excited! I'm so happy!
It's like we're really here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's just say it's absolutely delicious.
You've got a big belly.
It's a big bowl of rice.
Oh, uh, right...
There's a Tokai set. We have a Tokai set.
Oh, this one! Wow, there's so many!
Tendai... I was wondering about Tendai.
It looks like they let you eat inside, right?
Yes.
Let's eat. Shall we eat?
Yes!
Welcome.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you.
Please wait while I look over there again.
You're very kind.
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you so much for coming to our country.
It's a wonderful place.
It is, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
This is the kind of place I'd like to live.
Hmm?
I want to live there.
Seriously?
Yes.
It's pretty much like that, isn't it?
You have a small face, but...
Wow. You should definitely go.
They're so nice.
You should definitely go.
Hey, it's a great place to work.
I'll work hard.
Yeah, I'll work hard.
Let's work hard.
I'll do my best.
Yes. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Isn't the image of Rinec kind of dry?
Yes, it is.
Please try one.
May I?
The one you didn't order.
It's not ordered.
Thank you very much.
Try a mouthful.
Breast meat.
This is with Arb Salt.
Plenty and plenty of
Spice
I've never had that before.
The reactions are amazing.
Oh, my God.
It makes you happy.
I'm so glad I made it.
Thank you so much.
Really? Really?
Yes, I'm sure.
Please eat the squid.
Bon appétit.
The breast meat while it's still warm.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit!
Hot.
Mm-hmm.
Mmm?
Soft.
Delicious.
Oh, my God.
Stylish face.
Okazaki was fashionable.
Fashionable.
Bon appétit!
Soft
My first meal.
It stings.
I've risked my life for this.
It's done.
I'm Serte Masaki.
Here you go.
Where is it?
This is amazing!
Here's the meat with sweet sauce.
Thank you very much.
Yuuka-san.
It's a piece of meat.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit.
Is it good?
Amazing.
Blue.
It's filled with...
Potatoes and
and thighs
with sweet sauce
Five fried potatoes.
It's a lot of food.
Looks delicious.
Looks so good!
Can I eat this?
I'll hold it for you.
I'm nervous.
I'm going to eat it right here.
Oh, my God.
It's live!
the sweet sauce is the best!
Looks so good!
I ordered a piece of meat.
Cubed meat.
Cubes, right?
Bon appétit!
I've never had shingles before!
What flavor?
I'm trying to say what it tastes like.
What does it taste like?
I don't know. Texture?
Correct.
A little bit of the status quo.
Spicy.
It's a little different.
It's a little bit different from the breast you just gave me.
It's a little more...
It's a little more tender.
It's so good!
Share Happish!
Looks delicious!
This one is.
I had the thigh with sweet sauce.
I had a hard time deciding.
The most popular flavor
The most popular flavor was the sweet sauce.
I'll have it!
Wow! It's so crispy. Good sound.
Ooh!
Delicious!
Crunchy!
Thank you!
I'm super happy when I hear you say it's delicious.
The flavor of the raw dough is exquisite, and the taste is delicious.
Yes, it is.
Delicious!
You have a face, don't you?
Tebasaki.
Wow! It's huge!
One of the biggest in Japan.
25cm.
It looks like it's bowing.
It's cute.
Looks delicious.
Delicious!
Sweet and spicy.
The sweet and spicy sauce is so delicious.
Looks delicious.
But it looks like it will go down easy.
Bon appétit.
Caught in Okazaki. It's Okazaki's local chicken.
It's a bit chewy, isn't it?
The one before was different.
It's muscle.
It's a selfie, because he's running around.
He's got muscles.
Wow!
I want muscles.
Look from the side, Mitsuki's face is the same.
It's cute, like she's bowing.
They look good together.
The size suits you.
The sauce is really good.
Everyone loves sweet and spicy sauce.
It's tender and delicious.
The salt looks amazingly good too.
I haven't seen all of them.
I wanted to eat all 15 kinds.
Try it.
Eat, eat.
Go ahead.
Bon appétit.
Delicious.
Ready?
Yes, it's good.
It's kind of cool.
It's delicious.
Crunchy.
Very tasty.
Everything is delicious.
Is it really delicious?
It's so good.
It's good. It's good.
It's delicious.
So, you know, you can't have a fixed idea that it has to be hot.
It's just a preconceived notion.
I'm sure it looks big.
At first, people made fun of me for making this.
But that's how it is.
When I tried it, I thought it looked different.
It's delicious.
Why are they so crispy, Kate?
They've been fried for more than 30 minutes.
It's amazing.
And then you let them cool?
Yes, yes.
You know, quick freezing.
I can see why they're so crispy.
It's delicious.
Delicious.
I'll bring about 3,000 of them.
It's delicious.
But you can't.
Yes.
We've just arrived at the Okazaki City Tourist Association place.
I'm so glad. I took a walk.
Yes, we just took a walk, and the fact that we are allowed to go inside...
Let's go in.
I'm nervous
Thank you very much
I'm sorry to bother you
Score.
Oh, my God.
That's, uh, 23 meters.
And this is the newest.
Cute!
It's cute.
It's nice.
Hey, I didn't come here for a minute.
I'm very happy in Okazaki. I'm very happy.
I'm sorry for a minute.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Oh, score.
Score.
Unfallen?
This is cute.
It was a project.
It said something about QR.
I'm new here too.
Yay!
I'm here for the first time, too.
I'm here for the first time too.
Yay!
I want to ring my bell.
Ring?
었다
I want to ring
Upper part
the top part
Þóng Þóng Þóng
came
Here it comes!
here we go!
Oh, my God.
Look at that!
200 yen
That's great!
Oh, I won!
Of course I did.
For real.
Oh!
RV.
For now.
Good luck.
Ooh!
You did it!
Oh, my gosh, it's just like I left it.
Yay!
You wore it today.
I wore orange today.
I'm lefty.
That's great.
I'm Miku.
I see you.
I saw you.
I tried not to.
Mai mai mai!
I see you.
Ah, Shibayu-san?
Mr. Shiba Yu?
It's Shibayu-san.
He's cute.
So small.
He's got a cool way of showing it.
Yeah, it's cool.
You're looking good.
Thank you very much.
The town of Okazaki is really warm, the people, everyone is warm.
It's amazing.
I made eye contact with Shibayu-san.
That's great.
Amazing!
Wow, wow, wow!
I saw Mr. Courtney Ware in various places.
It's amazing!
It's warm, isn't it?
It really felt different on everyone's skin.
Oh, here we are!
We're here.
I guess this is where we change planes.
Transfer.
Yes, so I'd like to announce where we're going next.
Oh!
Yes, I would like to go to a place called Okudo no Jinya.
Yay!
I'm so happy!
Tetsuya and Minami Minegishi have reported on this place quite a bit.
Video?
This is the place where Tetsuya and Minako Minegishi made a lot of reports?
I'm so happy!
The voices...
There are a lot of voices.
Yeah, yeah.
So I'd like to go there.
Yes, ma'am.
Separate
And the car
Oh, yeah.
Hands change.
Yes, Mizuki and I will be riding in the orange Tetsuya's car this time!
Yes, sir.
Let's get going.
Let's go!
Yes, I'm in Tetsuya's car now.
Yes!
Amazing!
It's so comfortable.
Comfortable, isn't it?
You can see a little orange from the inside.
Oh, this is it.
Right there.
It's cute.
Cute.
We're on our way to the Okudo camp.
Yes.
We're having fried chicken in the car, too.
It looks like a very comfortable ride, doesn't it?
Yes, sir!
Talk to me!
Talk!
It's a little bit... It's very good.
It was good, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was.
Ta-da!
Yes! We've arrived at the recommended boat shop!
Beautiful!
It's amazing! The drops are delicious!
It's amazing! Amazing!
It looks like we can feed the love that Tetsuya-san opened here.
Let's get to it!
I'm so happy!
Behind you.
I feel the sound, the presence of voices!
I feel the presence of a voice!
I'm excited!
Let's do it!
Oh, my God! There it is!
Is it this big?
Wow!
You guys, this is...
I'm sure it's gonna spread now.
Here you go!
Let's give it up!
Oh, my God, there's so many!
This is fun!
Here you go, yellow!
Wow!
Oh, my gosh! That's great!
Cheetos!
He's eating! He's eating!
Yeah!
Wow!
Stop fighting, everybody!
In the back, too!
No one even noticed.
Wow! Wow!
Oh, my God, they're climbing up the rocks!
They're eating rocks! Rocks!
He's eating a rock!
Oh, my God!
I mean, how much alike are they? It's like...
Wow!
Gold dust!
It's amazing! It's stuck!
Don't eat it!
If we do it here.
If we do it here, it's gonna be a hot spot.
Look!
There's a hot spot!
I want you to have it!
Oh, my God!
No, that's why it's great,
To one, to one, to one,
One, one, one,
To one,
Alone,
Alone type
What do you mean?
Oh, my mouth.
Wow!
Oh! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, it looks like Leno! Just like Leno!
Oh, my God, so much!
So much,
Aaah!
It looks like it's coming up on land.
It's coming up.
It's coming up!
It's coming up
That's great.
Thank you. Thank you.
I hope you're not too full.
I'm sure I am.
I'm exercising.
He's still eating.
He's eating as fast as he can feed.
Wow.
That's cute.
I'm scared.
He came so fast.
Wow.
Cute.
I'm full.
I'm so full.
Scary.
Very scary.
Thank you very much.
Wow! So many pearls. So many pearls.
So many pearls! So cute! I'm so happy!
So many pearls! I got so many!
I'm so happy! We got a lot of them!
I'm so happy! So nice!
From today I want to wear a potato on Tetsuya's arm!
Mini talk!
Orange mini talk!
Thanks again!
See you in the next video!
Now I'd like to head to the next location.
Next up is the last place we're going to talk about.
Last month, RYO-san, who will be on the air this time, opened a cake shop.
Let's go there!
Let's go!
Let's jump!
We've arrived at La Maison Biard!
One jump!
Wow!
It's so beautiful!
I love it!
It's what I've always wanted.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Your belly is a cake belly too.
You have a sweet mouth.
I'll be there!
I'll be there.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Sorry, everyone.
Let's eat.
Thank you very much.
My favorite.
they won't buy it
They won't buy it.
It's kinda good.
It's a little tasty.
Tasty.
Delicious.
Yum, yum, yum,
What's this?
Kocher.
Is this Kocher?
Kocher-ish.
Yes. Nice to meet you.
Thank you very much.
Well...
We have prepared all the cakes that will be served today.
It smells so good and sparkles.
It shines brighter than jewels.
It's reflective, isn't it?
Maybe it reflects on you, on your face
The space is so interesting that it makes you sound like an actress.
I'd be an actress.
I'm supposed to choose one of these.
I can't choose.
I don't know how I've ever chosen life
I don't know how to choose
I'm lost in it all.
Shortcake, tart, chutney, basque
Basque cheese sticks are something
Delicious
We'll play rock-paper-scissors to see who wins.
Or maybe I'd rather lose.
I can't choose.
You want to go?
First one is "goo", then "rock, paper, scissors".
It's Aiko, right? It's Aiko, right? It's Aiko, right?
You win.
First, "goo", then "rock, paper, scissors".
What shall I do?
What should I do?
From Yuukapyon
Wait, wait, wait!
Oh my God, what do I do?
How do we choose?
I'm sure I'm probably the most friendless of the four of us.
Well then...
I'll go with the one you tried.
Great.
I'll take that one.
Next, Ai.
Ai.
Wait a minute.
What should I do? Come on.
What the hell are you doing here for an hour?
No, it took me two weeks.
You're right.
Nana nana nana heppolte bam bam bam bam hominy bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam
I'll take these rice cakes, then.
I'll take this one, please.
So cute!
Or cheesecake.
Great.
Or cheesecake. Looks good.
It all looks good.
I love it.
It's so good.
Looks so good.
I'm looking forward to it.
Sparkling.
Looks delicious.
With the mask on.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Bon appétit!
Looks good.
Looks delicious!
It melts in your mouth.
It's too good!
This white part is so melty and thick!
Mask!
I'll have some too.
Freddy.
I'll go first.
Matt, it's too good!
It's like a mousse.
Bon appétit.
Yum!
Delicious!
Tea mousse?
Melt in your mouth!
It's kind of chocolatey.
It's covered with some kind of chocolate.
It's gone.
Looks amazingly delicious!
Strawberry tart
I've never seen anything like it before.
It's so cute!
It's like a tiara!
Crunchy and super delicious!
Looks delicious!
Custard
I love the custard!
It's so good!
Looks delicious
Hi, you're going to love it.
I'm looking for it.
Delicious!
It tastes like a shortcake!
The cream inside is so soft!
It's so soft and creamy!
It sure looks fluffy!
The ultimate moist sponge and melt-in-your-mouth cream flavor!
Delicious!
It's a delicious taste that really comes through.
Thank you very much for the cake!
That's why you had it, isn't it?
Thank you so much for the food.
It was delicious.
It was very delicious.
It was a wonderful end to a wonderful trip in a stylish space.
I was able to do it from the car in the morning.
We went to so many places in one day.
How was it? How was it?
You can see it all in one day.
No, I got to see more than that.
I've been doing this for 30 years.
I'm really happy that you spent such a fulfilling day with us.
I'm also very grateful to Tetsuya-san for coming up with the plan.
I've always wanted to come to Okazaki, but it's not often that I get a chance to go there on a private trip.
I am very happy that we were able to take this opportunity to visit Okazaki together.
I love Okazaki!
Thank you so much!
I want to come back again at the end, I want to come to all the members.
Thank you for seeing us off at the end.
I just want to say thank you so much for all your hard work.
I want to do my best.
I even signed your autograph.
So years from now, you'll have a face like, "Look at me!
I want to work even harder to become a group that can do that.
It was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much for the wonderful presentation.
Thank you very much.
If you enjoyed this video, please subscribe to our channel and leave a comment!
Thank you very much!
That's all for now.
This is Hikojo Palace.
Bye bye.